[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I went to my closet to get dressed for work, but this threw me into a panic due to my decidophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Making decisions", "incorrect_answers": ["Shoes", "Clothing", "Getting undressed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the dangerous active volcano located in the Western Highlands of Guatemala?", "correct_answer": "Santa Maria", "incorrect_answers": ["Santa Lucia", "Santa Fernanda", "Santa Beatrice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The backgrounds in Bambi are often in soft focus. Which statement explains why?", "correct_answer": "It helped put the focus on the main characters.", "incorrect_answers": ["Disney wanted a serene feel to all the scenes.", "It was a style developed by the Disney studios in the 1920s", "The technology at the time would not allow for great resolution."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do cats suddenly race through the house?", "correct_answer": "They have an overflow of pent-up energy.", "incorrect_answers": ["They feel a change in the weather.", "They want to get your attention.", "They feel the presence of a ghost."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A woman has 7 children. Half of them are boys. Can this be true?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Popeyes merge with KFC in 1989?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nick Fury is the alter ego of Wolfsbane.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these economic terms does not denote restriction of international trade, i.e. the free flow of goods between nations?", "correct_answer": "The General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade", "incorrect_answers": ["Trade quotas", "Non-tariff trade barriers", "Import tariffs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first player for the Tampa Bay (Devil) Rays?", "correct_answer": "Tony Saunders", "incorrect_answers": ["Chuch LaMar", "Wilson Alvarez", "Larry Rothschild."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Christine Jorgensen most famous for?", "correct_answer": "transgender surgery", "incorrect_answers": ["voice-over actor/singer", "mystery writer", "photography"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Mrs. Robinsons first name in the film The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "It was never mentioned in the movie.", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrea", "Gwen", "Jenny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars character asked the question, Are you an angel??", "correct_answer": "Anakin Skywalker", "incorrect_answers": ["Queen Amidala", "Obi Wan Kenobi", "Jar Jar Binks"]}]